Business Ephemera Collection
Hartford History Center, Hartford Public Library
- Trade cards, Business Cards, Miscellaneous Small Advertisements
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 188-?; One card with a child, a bird, flowers, and insects (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 188-?; Two cards with women in short dresses (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 189-?; Three cards featuring two women and a clown (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 189-?; Three cards with figures in costume (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 189-?; One card with figures in costume (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 189-?; Three cards with children and animals (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 188-?; Two different designs (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 189-?; Two cards with comic figures and gold background (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 188-?; Two miniature cards with different designs (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 1881; Two different cards with 1881 calendars and views depicting Summer and Autumn (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 189-?; One card with a dog (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 188-?; One card featuring a duck sitting on a frog that has swallowed an egg (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 188-?; One floral design (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 188-?; Three different designs: "Spring Suits to Order" (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 189-?; One card featuring baseball players (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 189-?; Two different designs: "Imported Goods in Ready Made Clothing." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 189-?; Six cards with comic figures playing musical instruments (three the same) (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 1879; One card with a woman walking a dog (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 189-?; One card with a portrait of George Washington (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 189-?; Two cards featuring women in canoes (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gemmill, Burnham and Company, 189-?; Postcard with collision of two high wheel bicycles (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Postcard, Gink Letam Non-Profit Corporation, 198-?; "At Gink Letam--God is Love / Christ is the Answer." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, John B. Gleason, 18--?; "Tonsorial Artist. Special pains taken with Children's Hair Cutting & Ladies' Shampooing." Four different floral designs. (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Globe Clothing Company, 1888?; "Startling Sacrifice! All Mark-Down Sales Insignificant compared to this Wondrous Chance." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Business card, Goddard & Blair, 199-?; Business card of Stephen B. Goddard (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Ye Golden Grill, 190-?; "Hartford's Largest and Most Popular Café." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Goldschmidt, Stern and Mandelbaun, 186-?; "Yankee Notions, Zephyr Worsteds, Corsets, Etc." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Edward Goodman, 1855?; "Yankee Notions, Zephyr Worsteds, Corsets, Etc." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Postcard, Miss Goodrich, 190-; "Manicuring and Chiropody, Facial Massage, Chin Belts for Sale, Shampooing and Hair Dressing, Pompadour and Switches, Marcel Waving A Specialty." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, C.S. Goodwin and Son, 188-?; "Established 1804. Boots and Shoes of every description." Two designs featuring circus performers (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, L.H. Goodwin, 187-?; Three different designs (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, L.H. Goodwin, 187-?; "Dealer in Drugs, Medicines, Toilet Articles, etc. Choice Brands of Cigars a Specialty." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Postcard, Goodyear Service Store, 1940; "Free American Flags with Suction Cup Holder for your Truck, Auto or Home." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Postcard, Gospel Hall, 1990?; "All are welcome and no collectins or donations ever solicited or accepted." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Business card, Gospel Hall, 18--?; Business card of W. D. Cornwall (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Postcard, Grand Theatre, 1917; "Sincerely hoping your Christmas will be jolly and that you will sail along an untroubled sea of success for many years." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, E.L. Graves, 18--; "Orders promptly attended to." Four different floral designs. (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, E.L. Graves, 18--; Image of an old woman and her shadow. Copyright Bufford, Boston (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, John W. Gray and Company, 188-?; "Rubber drinking cups, pocket match boxes, tobacco bags, Goodyear's Rubber Goods." Three different designs. (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, John W. Gray and Company, 188-?; "Footballs, from $1.25 to $2.50 each." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, John W. Gray and Company, 188-?; Advertisement for the Universal Clothes Wringer featuring an African American woman (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Business cards, Greater Hartford Convention and Visitor Bureau, 198-?; Business cards of H. Catherine Ladd, Executive Director, John Chapin, Vice President, Communications, and Joan R. Cowles, Convention Services Manager (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Gregory's Dining, Lunch and Oyster Room, 187-?; Carte-de-visite with photograph of Gregory's Building with advertising on the back (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, H.R. Gridley, 189-?; "Fine Inside Shutters and Blinds, Hard Wood Work A Specialty. Also Glass, Oils, Paints, Colors, Putty, etc., etc." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, H.R. Gridley, 189-?; "Glass, Oils, Paints, Colors, Putty, etc., etc." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, Charles R. Griswold, 189-?; "For All Coughs, Colds, Bronchial Affections, and Troubles of the Throat and Lungs use Griswold's Pulmonary Balsam." (Box 9, Folder G)
  - Trade card, E. Habenstein, 189-?; Four different designs (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, E. Habenstein, 189-?; Two different floral designs: "Cottage Restaurant, Watch Hill, Westerly, R.I. Open from July 1st to September 15th." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, E. Habenstein's Elite Restaurant, 189-?; Two different designs, one in the shape of a fan (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Arthur Hack, 18--?; One floral design (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Louis Hahn, 191-?; "Keystone Improved Silver Watch Cases, Fine Jewelry, Sold Silverware, Silver Plated Ware, Clocks, &c." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, T.E. Hall, 18--?; "Cut Flowers and Floral Designs." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hannum's Business College, 188-?; "Branches taught, Book-keeping, Penmanship, Correspondence, Commercial Law, Arithmetic, Short Hand, Telegraphy and Typewriting." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hart, Merriam and Company, 188-?; E.T. Pratt, Proprietor. (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Hart, Merriam and Company, 189-?; "Carpets, Paper Hangings and Curtain Goods." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, City of Hartford - Office of Community Development and Planning, 198-?; Business card of David R. Hargreaves, Senior Administratie Analyst, Property Control Officer (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, City of Hartford - Department of Finance, 198-?; Business card of David R. Hargreaves, Senior Administratie Analyst, Property Control Officer (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, City of Hartford - Department of Public Works, 199-?; Business card of Husein Y. Osman, Project Engineer (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, City of Hartford - Department of Public Works, 199-?; Business card of Genaro Sepulveda, Principal Engineering Technician (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, City of Hartford - Police Department, 198-?; Business card of Patrick Toscano, Surveyor (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, City of Hartford - Engineering Services Bureau, 199-?; Business card of Thomas R. Moore, Jr., Lieutenant (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford 25c Store, 18--?; "For Holiday Gifts, Go to the Hartford 25c Store." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford 99c. Pavilion, 18--?; Four different floral designs (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Hartford Antiquarian Book Fair, 1983?; Thirty-five dealers of diverse stock exhibiting at the Connecticut Historical Society. (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, Hartford Architecture Conservancy, 198-?; Business card of Linda G. Harmon, Director of Development (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Hartford Automobile and Boat Supply Company, 190-?; "Victor Compound for Slipping Clutches and Brakes." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford Chemical Company, 188-?; Thirteen different designs. "Lavine for Washing. The Best and Cheapest Article ever offered to the Housekeeper." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Hartford Chemical Company, 189-?; Three cards with two designs featuring children: "Send us 12 Lavine Front Labels or 30 cents in cash or postage stamps and get one of our beautiful Panel Pictures…." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford Chemical Company, 188-?; Two different floral designs (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford Chemical Company, 188-?; Eight cut-out cards in the shape of animals (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford Chemical Company, 188-?; Four different miniature trade cards advertising "Lavine for Washing." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford Chemical Company, 188-?; Six different designs with gold backgrounds (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford Chemical Company, 188-?; One design with children and gold background (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford Chemical Works, 187-?; One card depicting children sailing toy boats in a washtub (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, Hartford Civic Center, 197-?; Business card for Administrative Offices (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, Hartford Courant, 198-?; Business card of Paula Parker, Assistant Metro Editor (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford Daily Courant, 1866; Card includes calendar for 1866 (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, Hartford Cycle Company, 19--?; Business card of David J. Post, Secretary-Treasurer (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford Cycle Company, 19--?; Trade card in the form of a playing card (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business cards, Hartford Downtown Council, 196-?; Business cards of Kathy T. Butler, Director of Operations/Development and Steven A. Lazaroff, Assistant Director for Events Programming. Two different designs. (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, Hartford Guides, 20--?; "A nonprofit organization making the downtown a friendlier place." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Hartford Equipment Company, 195-?; "Want a Free Demonstration… On Your Own Home Grounds?" (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, Hartford Files Society, 1976?; Anthony S. DeBonee, proprietor. "The Enhancement of Hartford's Heritage is a step towards its Preservation." 2 copies. (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Hartford Gun Shop, 1946?; Postcard featuring two dogs (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, The Hartford, 1893?; Alfred A. Pocock, Proprietor. "Will Open May 1." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, Hartford Magazine, 198-?; Business card of David J. Fleming, Advertising Representative (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Hartford Market Company, 191-?; "25% Saved on the Finest of all Food Products." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, Hartford National Bank and Trust Company, 197-?; Business card of Robert S. Carter, Jr., Vice President (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford One Price Clothing Company, 189-?; Eight cards with five different designs (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford One Price Clothing Company, 189-?; Two cards with heads of women in pink: "Come to our Fall Opening!" (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford One Price Clothing Company, 189-?; Three different designs (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Hartford One Price Clothing Company, 189-?; "Our Sixteenth Annual Exhibition Fall and Winter Clothing, now Open to the Public." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Hartford One Price Clothing Company, 189-?; "Overcoats! Overcoats!! Overcoats!!!" (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Hartford Patent Insole Company, 189-?; Postcard with view of Soldiers and Sailors Memorial Arch printed by the Kellogg & Bulkeley Company (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Hartford Phonograph Company, 191-?; "Headquarters for Everything in Records and Talking Machine Supplies." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, Hartford Public High School, 189-?; Business card of Joseph Hall, Principal (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, Hartford Public High School, 199-?; Business cards of Beverly A. Loughlin, Marlene M. Melcher, and Brenda Miller. Three different designs. (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business cards, Hartford Public Library, 199-?; Business cards of Beverly A. Loughlin, Marlene M. Melcher, and Brenda Miller. Three different designs. (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, Hartford Restaurant Association, 1990?; Business card of Elizabeth G. Shluger, Director (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford Sewing Machine, 189-?; Five different designs. Manufactured by the Weed Sewing Machine Company. (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford Sign Company, 18--?; G. E. Wightman and E. P. Forbes, Proprietors (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford Steam Saw Mill, 186-?; A. B. West, President; William B. Stevens, Secretary and Treasurer (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Hartford Wet Wash Laundry, 1913; Two designs with calendars for January 1913 and April 1913 (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford Wire Works, 187-?; J. Henry Martin, F. H. Crossthwaite, Proprietors (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hartford Wire Works, 189-?; "Everything You Can Ask for in Wire." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Hartford Woven Wire Mattress Company, 190-?; Henry Roberts, President and Treasurer; J. E. Godbee, Secretary (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Havey and Lewis Company, 1907?; Folder contains an eyeglass cleaner. Between 1907 and 1916 Harvey & Lewis advertised that they offered developing, printing, and enlarging for amateur photographers. (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hastings and Griswold, 186-?; E. G. Hastings and O. D. Griswold, Proprietors (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Charles E. Hatch, 18--?; "Chas. E. Hatch with Amos Larned & Co." Two different designs featuring farm scenes (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, H. Hawksworth, 189-?; One comic design: "A New Jersey Lillie." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, R.D. Hawley and Company, 188-?; Five comic designs featuring vegetables (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Hawley, Goodrich and Company, 1888; "Dear Sir:--Below find to-day's value of Grass, Clover and other Seeds…." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hawley, Goodrich and Company, 1870; Includes calendar for 1870. "Get your Neighbor to Subscribe." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Hawley, Goodrich and Company, 1875; Receipt for payment for subscription to the Connecticut Courant (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, J.P. Haynes and Company Boston Branch Tea and Grocery House, 187-?; One card with Oriental design (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, J.P. Haynes and Company Grocery House, 187-?; Card advertising Lactart (acid of milk) featuring a milkmaid (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, J.P. Haynes and Company Grocery House, 188-?; One card featuring jockeys riding rabbits (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, J.P. Haynes and Company Grocery House, 188-?; One card featuring jockeys riding rabbits (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Haynes and Simmons, 1881; Seven cards with 1881 calendars on the back (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, Hendsey's Old book Shop, 197-?; Note on back "Went out of business 6/77" (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, A.C. Hills, 187-? (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Howard G. Hills and Company, 18--?; "Jobbing of all kinds a specialty…. Door and window screens made and put up at short notice." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hills Archimedean Lawn-Mower Company, 1879-1880; "Emphatically the best and most beautiful Lawn Mower in the World." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, A.C. Hine Co., 198-?; Business card of Graham H. Hoagland (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, A.J. Hoadley, 188-?; "Ask for Fruit Tablets M'f'd by E. J. Hoadley, Hartford, Conn." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Hobby Shop, 191-?; Postcard with a view of the storefront (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, A. Hollander and Company, 188-?; Six cards with five different designs: "Fine Custom Goods a Specialty" (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, A. Hollander and Company, 188-?; Four different designs (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, A. Hollander and Company, 188-?; Business card of Samuel Hollander (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, A. Hollander Sons, 1899?; "Fine Custom Work A Specialty" (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Sam Hollander, 187-?; "Also a Fine Assortment of Jewelry." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, Horan's Flowers, 19--?; Thomas F. Horan, Mary Margaret Horan, Proprietors. "Expressing Your Thoughtfulness With Flowers, Plants, Fruit and Gifts since 1909." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, C.B. Holt and Company, 188-?; Three cards with oriental subjects: "The Caravan," "Suleiman Pasha," "Arabian Mail Carrier." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Business card, C.B. Holt and Company, 188-?; Seven cards with humorous subjects (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade cards, E. Horner, 186-?; Two cards. "A Select Stock of Embroideries, Laces, Zephyr Worsteds, Hosiery, Cambric and Muslin Corsets, Edgings and Insertions, Scarfs, Collars, Sleeves, Sets, &c." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Invitation, Horsfall and Rothschild, 1895; "We take pleasure in announcing our Spring Opening of Fine Tailor Made Clothing and Overcoats." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcards, Horsfall and Rothschild, 19--?; Two postcards with view of "Old Newgate" Prison, one printed in green, the other in black (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Horsfall and Rothschild, 1902?; "The Smart Stein-Bloch Clothing." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, L.M. Hotchkiss, 185-?; "Shawls, Silks, Satins, Bombazines, Alpacas, &c." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Household Fuel Corporation, 1930?; "Order your fuel before you are out of it--Any day storms may slow up deliveries." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hub Clothing House, 188-?; Three designs featuring women printed in green on gold backgrounds (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hub Clothing House, 188-?; Seven different designs (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hub Clothiers, 187-?; Three different designs. "Our Team: W. C. Burpee, J. D. Darling, E. S. Kendall, F. W. Kendall, C.V. Cornish." (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Postcard, Huntsinger's, 1908; "Schooltime is at hand. Wouldn't you better decide now to enter Huntsinger's?" (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Charles F. Hurd and Company, 188-?; Two different designs (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Trade card, Hurd and Mellen, 189-?; Three cards with portraits of Presidents. Partners are Charles F. Hurd and Moses Mellen. (Box 9, Folder H)
  - Busines card, Immanuel Congregational Church, 198-?; Business card of Robert L. Edwards, Minister Emeritus. Edwards retired in 1980. (Box 9, Folder I)
  - Postcard, India Store, 190-?; Store opened in 1904 (Box 9, Folder I)
  - Business card, Institute of Cultural Affairs, 197-?; Business card of Robert E. Hanson (Box 9, Folder I)
  - Trade card, Ives, 188-?; Two different designs, one with frogs holding a balloon, the other with a stork and snake (Box 9, Folder I)
  - Business card, the J.P. Morgan, 198-?; Business card of Karen McCredie, Catering Sales Manager (Box 9, Folder J)
  - Trade card, Jacobs & Forbes, 188-?; Two different winter scenes (Box 9, Folder J)
  - Trade card, Jacobs & Forbes, 188-?; One humorous design featuring small boys (Box 9, Folder J)
  - Trade card, Johnson and Ransom, 185-?; W. M. Johnson and H. C. Ransom, Proprietors (Box 9, Folder J)
  - Trade card, Mrs. R.M. Jones, 18--?; One floral design (Box 9, Folder J)
  - Trade card, Jones and Little, 189-?; Partners are R. M. Jones and H. B. Little. "Gear Patterns and Cogging, Wood Turning, Scroll Sawing, and Shop Jobbing." (Box 9, Folder J)
  - Business card, Jumping Frog, 198-?; "Hartford's only second-hand bookstore." (Box 9, Folder J)
  - Postcard, O.W. Kapitke, 191-?; "Don't send your friends trashy, cheap valentines, but send them something that will make their good opinion of you last a long time. Send them a nice piece of jewelry." (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, Kashmann's Furnishing House, 188-?; Two different designs (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, Kashmann's Furnishing House, 192-?; "Give us a Call before you Purchase." (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, Kellogg and Buckingham, 185-?; Partners are Robert H. Kellogg and Hiram Buckingham (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, Kellogg and Butler, 188-?; One floral design (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, E.N. Kellogg and Company, 187-?; Partners are E. N. Kellogg, Austin Dunham, and A. C. Dunham (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, Kellogg, Douglas and Seidler, 186-?; "W. Bromley Keeney, with Kellogg, Douglas & Seidler." (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, Rodney Kellogg, 188-?; "Pure No. 1 Pervian Guano; Coe's Super Phosphate of Lime; Pure Bone Dust; Land Plaster; Genuine Lodi Poudrette; Castor Pummace; Ag'l Lime; Fish Guano." (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, E.S. Kendall and Company, 1889; "Hub" Clothing House (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, Kennedy and Way, 184-?; "Cutlery, Steel, Nails, and Shovels, also, Agents for the Sale of Domestic Hardware, Brass Wire, Sheet Brass, Malleable Iron, Collins Axes, Miscellaneous Tools, &c. &c." (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, R.P. Kenyon and Company, 1875?; Card features portraits of Dwight L. Moody and Ira D. Sankey (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, R.P. Kenyon and Company, 189-?; Two images of boys in uniform (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, Kenyon's Tea, Cofee and Spice House, 18--?; One design featuring a naked child (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Calendar and datebook, E.S. Kibbe Company, 1926; Book with 1926 and 1927 calendars, maps, and "useful information." (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, Charles King, 188-?; Headquarters for the 'Good News' Portable Range." (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, Horace H. King, 187-?; One floral design (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, Ralph King and Son, 1877?; "All Kinds of Carriages and Wheel Work, from the Connecticut Oak & Hickory." (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, King Dental Company, 191-?; "Teeth? Full Set $5.50." (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, Kingsley and Miller, 188-?; Proprietors are K. C. Kingsley and H. G. O. Miller (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Postcard, L.S. Knoek, 192-?; "Goodrich Hi-Press Rubber Footwear for Fishermen." (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Trade card, Henry Kohn, 188-?; One Japanese design (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Business card, H.P. Koppelmann, 1980; "A Single Source for all your Paperbacks." (Box 9, Folder K)
  - Brochure, [J.G. Lane?], 19--?; Brochure listing brands of whiskey and other liquor available at 222, 224 and 226 State Street, but owner's name does not appear. J. G. Lane had a liquor license for this address in the early 1900s. (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Trade card, H.S. Larkum and Company, 1854?; On verso "Wm. F. Whittelsey / Salesman" (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Trade card, Amos Larned and Company, 187-?; Three different floral designs (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Trade card, W.J. Lawrence, 1876; Image depicts the Main Exhibition Building at the 1876 International Exhibition in Philadelphia. (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Trade card, Lazarus and Morris, 1875; "Perfected Spectacles and Eye-Glasses, Opera Glasses, Optical Instruments and Drawing Materials." (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Trade card, Leach and Kingsbury, 1868?; Dealers in Pharmaceutical Preparations, Toilet Articles, Wines for Medicinal Use, Mineral Waters, Etc. (Box 9, Folder L)